<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2024-03-21T19:56:16+11:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Joe Zhou’s World</title><subtitle>## Writing  ## Books  ## Readings  ## Fun  ## Diary   ## Movie  ## Sharing</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Spider Dairy</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/cat2/2024/03/17/Spider-Dairy.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Spider Dairy" /><published>2024-03-17T19:15:29+11:00</published><updated>2024-03-17T19:15:29+11:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/cat2/2024/03/17/Spider-Dairy</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/cat2/2024/03/17/Spider-Dairy.html"><![CDATA[<p><b>Monday 2024/03/17</b></p>

<p>My life changed when a lady carrying a baby sister bottled me up in a transparent plastic container. I wonder why she has captured me. The most likely reason was because of my glowing, purple-tipped legs and yellow spots.</p>

<p>The mother dumped me into a bag of fruit and veggies and trotted somewhere. As she walked, I could feel her feet bumping against mine and the bag shaking like a tremendous earthquake.</p>

<p>Not long afterwards, the earthquake stopped. I heard a door open quietly. At that moment, I felt a mix of fear and curiosity rushing within me. The woman dropped the bag on the floor and after putting all the groceries inside the fridge, she took hold of my bottle and placed it on the kitchen table.</p>

<p>I took a vast look around. I saw a grey, soft sofa, a big-screened television, a grand dining table, cool lights, baby toys and thick books. For extra information, I spotted a bowl of fruit on my left side and a jar of peanut butter and Nutella on the right. After, the lady raced outside in the rush.</p>

<p>Since the woman was not there, I tried to escape. However, from gnawing walls to kicking sides, none of them seemed to work. Exhausted, I drifted to slumber. I awoke to the sight of a creeping-looking child. He had his school bag on and a threatening hairstyle. His grin was so menacing that I thought he was going to penetrate something sharp into me or mash me up into a disgusting paste……</p>

<p>TO BE CONTINUED…</p>

<p><img src="/assets/spider-dairy-1.jpg" alt="image tooltip here" /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="Cat2" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Monday 2024/03/17]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Welcome to my website !!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/cat2/2024/03/17/about-this-website.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to my website !!" /><published>2024-03-17T19:15:29+11:00</published><updated>2024-03-17T19:15:29+11:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/cat2/2024/03/17/about-this-website</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/cat2/2024/03/17/about-this-website.html"><![CDATA[<p><b>Welcome to my website</b></p>

<p>This is my first web blog using Jekyll, as an pratical way to show my writing scripts and stories .</p>

<p><b>The Design</b></p>

<p><ins> Spider Dairy </ins></p>

<p><ins> The Ants Revange </ins>        coming soon</p>

<p><ins> Fables </ins>           coming soon</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="Cat2" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to my website]]></summary></entry></feed>